[Music]
My name is Naman Sharma and I am working
as a Distribution Leader with ICICI Piden Life Insurance.
In fact, in last year's recruitment, I was in the
top five positions pan India.  2
years ago when I was in college I was
appointed as a management trainee in a company.
There I
also got the work of loan recovery.  Which was not my cup of
tea.
Then in October 2023 I got an opportunity to work as an
advisor with ICICI Prudential Life.
I worked hard here for 8
months.  Build your client base
and generate business.  Then ICICI
Pharma Life
gave me the opportunity to become a distribution leader.
Becoming a distribution leader means
becoming an entrepreneur.  When you are an
advisor, both your business and
client base are limited.  But when
you are a distribution leader, you
create a network of advisors under you.   The
more business the advisor does under DL,
the better the payout DL will
get multiplied.  After becoming a DL,
ICICI PDL Life
further enhanced my leadership skills by training me.  I
received off-field and on-field recruitment training which helped me understand
how I could strengthen relationship building.
Whether it's with my advisors
or with my clients.
In my recruitment strategy, I
go to MBA colleges.  Not only this, I
go to my local communities and approach retired persons
who want to start a new regular income to join this business.
And this way in the last one year
I recruited 22 advisors under me.  To
manage such a large team,
I hold advisor meetings every week.  I provide
product training.  I
motivate him and
accompany him on every client visit.
After getting DL in the last one year, my earnings
increased a lot.  I remember when my first
payout came, I transferred it to my father
which was a very proud moment for me.
I gifted a mobile to my mother.   I got
my sister a TV and I
bought myself a vehicle.  Whenever
I get paid, I invest it to secure my future.  The
biggest impact after becoming a doctor is
that I can manage work life balance in my life.
Because I am
working as an entrepreneur with ICICI Pt Life.  So now I am
able to give time to my family and friends also.  This distribution leader role is for advisors who want to grow in their careers and
build their businesses.
Today I have become a successful DL
, but my next target is to
become a Super DL so that I
can create more DLs under me and make myself
more successful.
[music]